gcu.ac.uk 2014-05-22

# Privacy Policy | Glasgow Caledonian University | Scotland, UK

### Privacy Policy

Glasgow Caledonian University is displaying this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: gcu.ac.uk, gcal.ac.uk, caledonian.ac.uk

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and gather broad demographic information. Our site's feedback form gives users the option to enter contact information (like their name and email address).

We use user's contact information from the registration form to send the user information about Glasgow Caledonian University. The user's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary.

### Cookies

**What are cookies?** ** **

A cookie is a small text file stored on a computer or mobile browser. They are used in a whole host of areas such as shopping baskets, personalised account areas and to collect anonymised information about site visitors. Information about cookies and how they work can be found at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

**Cookies on our website** ** **

**Cookies**

|   
---|---  
  
<script type="text/javascript">  
var gaJsHost = (("https:" == document.location.protocol) ? "https://ssl." : "http://www.");  
document.write(unescape("%3Cscript src='" + gaJsHost + "google-analytics.com/ga.js' type='text/javascript'%3E%3C/script%3E"));  
</script>  
<script type="text/javascript">  
var pageTracker = _gat._getTracker("UA-334467-1");  
pageTracker._trackPageview();  
</script>

| 

Google Analytics code used  
  
|   
  
**Google Analytics**

The University makes use of Google Analytics to produce statistics on website usage, which helps us to improve the site and your overall user experience. To do this, Google Analytics uses a cookie. All data is anonymous, though you can refuse the use of cookies by easily changing the options on your browser or you can opt-out by installing a [browser plug-in](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en) supplied by Google.

 [Google's Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html "The link to Google's Privacy Policy is an external website and will open in a new window.").

**Youtube**

This site also contains YouTube videos, which result in a third-party cookie being issued by '.youtube.com' only if the video is viewed. For more information on YouTube, please read [YouTube Advertising and You](http://www.youtube.com/t/interest_based_ads).

**Further information**

If you have any questions about this information, please email [webteam@gcu.ac.uk](mailto:webteam@gcu.ac.uk).

### Data Protection Act

Glasgow Caledonian University is registered under the Data Protection Act. The gathering, storage, use, release and disposal of personal information is regulated by the Data Protection Act 1998. [Find out more](http://www.gcal.ac.uk/dataprotection/)

**Further information:** If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site e-mail [webteam@gcu.ac.uk](mailto:webteam@gcu.ac.uk)
